<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Blog on Jonathan Cammack</title>
        <link>https://jonathancammack.333cloud.net/categories/blog/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Blog on Jonathan Cammack</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jonathancammack.333cloud.net/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Hello World!</title>
        <link>https://jonathancammack.333cloud.net/p/hello-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://jonathancammack.333cloud.net/p/hello-world/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;Hello World!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my website my name is Jonathan and here you will find my blogs and updates on my latest projects. This website will always be a work in progress along with my other projects but feel free to look around and read all you like.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Stack</title>
        <link>https://jonathancammack.333cloud.net/p/the-stack/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://jonathancammack.333cloud.net/p/the-stack/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;333cloud&#34;&gt;333Cloud&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The name 333Cloud originates from my birth hour being at 3:33PM I thought that was neat. These servers are for personal and learning purposes, so far I have learned a lot about servers and how to manage them.My server rack consists of a 2x4 skeleton and particle board walls. It was built in mind to be quiet and to fit in a room as makeshift furniture. It is still incomplete needing some adjustments to make it actually look decent however it keeps the rack quiet and cool especially with the box fan I installed in the back to move air throughout the whole chassis. The server rack consists of three enterprise servers and a 24-port gigabit network switch. Two servers being HP Proliants and one being a Dell Poweredge. I try to practice and sharpen my skills with these servers along with learning new ones. My main focus is to develop my own self-provisioning cloud that also contains my web server and game servers for personal purposes along with providing services to friends and family. The server hardware consists of one HP Proliant dl380p with 64GB of ram and dual Intel Xeon E5 2660 V1, one HP Proliant dl360p with 64GB of ram and dual Intel Xeon E5 2640 V1, one Dell Poweredge r210 with 4GB(will be upgraded to 16GB) and one Intel Xeon E3 3440, and a HP 24-port Gigabit switch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-services&#34;&gt;The Services&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the moment the services consist of four Minecraft servers, an Unturned server, a Space Engineers server, this website, Nextcloud, two TrueNAS servers for backup hosting,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-future-of-333cloud&#34;&gt;The Future of 333Cloud&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
